Guide to the Parents, Families and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG) records, 1972-2009.
Parents, Families and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG) records
- Series IX. Audiocassettes and Videocassettes
  - 1983 P-FLAG National Convention, New York, 7-10 October
    - Parents' and Parents Groups' role in the Gay/Lesbian Movement: communication with other groups, networking, support vs. participation in activities (Box 8, Folder 83-J)
      Andy Humm; Arleen Nelson
    - Politics: lobbying, administrative, legislation, funds, building support, coalitions, identification of allies and "enemies" (Box 8, Folder 83-K)
      Jeff Levi; Regina Arata
    - Discussion and Reflection: themes and project for Parents FLAG, building parent leadership, outreach to parents and friends, sharing concerns and ideas of delegates (Box 8, Folder 83-L)
      Adele Starr, moderator
    - Panel on Religious Issues: Biblical precepts, church/synagogue support and opposition, working for change (Box 8, Folder 83-M)
      Fr. John McNeill, Rev. Robert Davidson, rabbi Robert Goldberg; Harlan Adams
    - Awards Banquet Speakers (Box 8, Folder 83-N)
      Congressman Ted Teiss (D-NY); National Gay/Lesbian Task Force chair, Virginia Apuzzo
    - To Speak the Truth: touching personal story by wife of a gay man (Box 8, Folder 83-O)
      Jane Vennard
  - 1984 P-FLAG Convention, Denver, 28-30 September
    - Small Town Survival for Closeted Parents (Box 8, Folder 84-A)
      Mary Borhek, author
    - How to Keep Parents' Groups Healthy (Box 8, Folder 84-B)
      Dr. Tom Sauerman
    - Reaching Understanding: Mother/Daughter (Box 8, Folder 84-C)
      Henia and Dovida Goodman
    - Holistic Perspectives on Health Issues (Box 8, Folder 84-D)
      Randy Gunnoe, MA
    - Current Status of Social Research on Homosexuality (Box 8, Folder 84-E)
      Paula Murphy, PhD; Don Johnson, PhD
    - How Do New Parents Cope? Interview Results (Box 8, Folder 84-F)
      Marian Wirth and Carolyn Griffin
    - Coming of Age in the Gay/Lesbian Movement (Box 8, Folder 84-G)
      Ralph Rice and Carol Lease
    - The Heart of Every Successful Group: Good Facilitators (Box 8, Folder 84-H)
      Don Bossart, PhD; Judith Nelson, MS
    - Creative Ways of Educating the Public (Box 8, Folder 84-I)
      Gay Bossart, MA
    - The Denver Church Model: A Mormon Comes Out; The Julian Rush Story; A Theology Student Looks at the Bible and Homosexuality; Resources for Dealing with the Conservative Church Community (2 tapes) (Box 8, Folder 84-J)
      Don Johnson, PhD; George Christi; Jane Vennard; Elinor Kirby
    - Are Long-Term Relationships Possible? (Box 8, Folder 84-K)
      Don McMaster and Nolan Oltjenbruns (together 8 years)
    - Seeing is Believing... And therein Lies the Rub!: Media Portrayal of Racism, Sexism and Homophobia (Box 8, Folder 84-L)
      Theresa Malumphy
    - Update on AIDS (Box 8, Folder 84-M)
      Rev. Julian Rush
    - "Windfire": Gay/Lesbian Teenagers' Group (Box 8, Folder 84-N)
      Franklin Jenkins; Robert Hansen; David Shepherd
    - Divided and Conquered: Sexism in the Gay Movement and Homophobia in the Women's Movement (Box 8, Folder 84-O)
      Dr. Susan Schafer
    - Legal Problems Unique to Gays/Lesbians (Box 8, Folder 84-P)
      Paul Hunter, JD; Libby Comeaux, JD
    - Spouses from Two Perspectives (Box 8, Folder 84-Q)
      Jane Vennard, former wife of a gay man; Rev. Jane Spahr, former wife of a straight man
    - Why Do We Avoid Sexual Stereotypes? Our son, the "Queen", and Our Daughter, The "Diesel Dyke" (Box 8, Folder 84-R)
      Steve Kent
    - Reaching Out to Minority Parents (Box 8, Folder 84-S)
      Tim Wilson; Chip Crawford
    - Note: tape 84-T does not exist
    - Spiritual Dimensions of the Gay/Lesbian Journey (Box 8, Folder 84-U)
      Rev. Julian Rush; Rev. Jane Adams Spahr
    - The Issue of Realities: Human Rights; The Knowns and Unknowns about Homosexuality in the Medical/Scientific Community (Box 8, Folder 84-V)
      Federico Pena, Mayor of Denver; Dr. Mary Calderone, SIECUS
    - The Issue of Rights: Feminism, Sexism, and Homophobia; Homosexuality in the Black Community (Box 8, Folder 84-W)
      Dr. Marjorie Leidig; Dr. James Tinney
    - The Issue of Responsibilities: Reaching the Religious Community (Box 8, Folder 84-X)
      Dr. Sally Geis; Dr. Tom Sauerman; Rev. Merrill Follansbee
    - Concert by P-FLAG Festival Chorus (Box 8, Folder 84-Y)
      Directed by Susan Anderson
    - Awards Banquet, Entertainment, and Closing Address (Box 8, Folder 84-Z)
      By Bishop Melvin Wheatley, newly retired Bishop of the Rocky Mountain Conference of the United Methodist Church: "There Goes Another One"
    - Concert by Henia and Dovida Goodman (Box 8, Folder 84-1)
      With Ann Wallace
    - Rosh Hashanah Service (Box 8, Folder 84-2)
      Led by members of Tikvat Shalom
    - Ecumenical Worship Service (Box 8, Folder 84-3)
  - 1984 Atlantic Avenue United Methodist Church Conference on Homosexuality, Long Beach, CA, 17 March
    - Facts and Misconceptions about Homosexuality (Box 8, Folder 84-LB1)
      Dr. Evelyn Hooker
    - Gay Health Issues (Box 8, Folder 84-LB2)
      Neil Schram, MD
    - Biblical and Theological Background of Homosexuality (Box 8, Folder 84-LB3)
      Dr. Ignacio Castuera, Los Angeles District Superintendent, United Methodist Church
    - How to Parent the Adolescent Gay (Box 8, Folder 84-LB4)
      Rev. Albert Ogle and Adele Starr
    - How to Come Out as Parents (Box 9, Folder 84-LB5)
      Rev. Leo Nieto and Agnes McLaughlin
    - Homosexuality: My Own Story (Box 9, Folder 84-LB6)
      Lyle Loder, Diane Crocker, and Adele Starr
  - 1985 P-FLAG National Convention, Atlanta, GA, 25-28 October
    - How to Raise Funds (Box 9, Folder 85-1)
      Agnes McLaughlin, Norma Coates
    - How to Help Parents Cope and Beyond (Box 9, Folder 85-2)
      Marian and Arthur Wirth, Carolyn Griffin
    - How to Deal with the AIDS Crisis (two tapes) (Box 9, Folder 85-3)
      Ken South, Don Smith, Daren Shane
    - How to Start a New Group (Box 9, Folder 85-4)
      Amy and Richard Ashworth
    - How to Run a Good Meeting (Box 9, Folder 85-5)
      Carol and Bob Blaustone
    - How to Help Our Children with the Church (Box 9, Folder 85-6)
      Bishop and Mrs. Melvin Wheatley, United Methodist Church; David Chuning
    - How to Put on a "Coming Out to Your Parents" Workshop (Box 9, Folder 85-7)
      Tom Sauerman and panel
    - How to Involve the Gay Community (Box 9, Folder 85-8)
      Nancy Keene and panel
    - Ecumenical Worship Service (Box 9, Folder 85-9)
      Rev. John Storey, Clifton Presbyterian Church
    - AIDS (2 tapes - second tape includes banquet conclusion, see 85-12) (Box 9, Folder 85-10)
      Dr. James Curran, Center for Disease Control, Atlanta
    - New Board Luncheon (Box 9, Folder 85-11)
      Rosemary Kuropat, National Gay Task Force
    - Banquet (Box 9, Folder 85-12)
      Nancy Roth, Gay Rights National Lobby; Atlanta Gay Men's Chorus; Atlanta Lambda Corale; Sid Shier
  - 1986 P-FLAG National Convention, Portland, OR, 19-21 September
    - Couples (Box 9, Folder 86-A)
      Peggy Hackenbruck, MD; Donald Weston, PhD
    - Small Town Survival and Successful Rap Groups (Box 9, Folder 86-B)
      Katie and Harry Urbanek
    - Networking with the Gay and Lesbian Community (Box 9, Folder 86-C)
      Nancy Keene; Shirley Weaver; Sara Winter; Elinor Kirby; Carol Anderson; Judith Nelson
    - Helping Kids Who Love Someone Gay (Box 9, Folder 86-D)
      Rebecca Sinclair, MS
    - Youth Groups (Box 9, Folder 86-E)
      Frank Jenkins, MA and members or former members of Windfire, Portland, OR
    - Discrimination in the Workplace (Box 9, Folder 86-F)
      David Biviano
    - Substance Abuse in the Gay/Lesbian Community (Box 9, Folder 86-G)
      Susan Shepherd
    - Homosexuality and the New Testament: An Issue of Contexts (Box 9, Folder 86-H)
      Dr. George Edwards
    - Portland Hotlines: Being Responsive to a Community's Needs (Box 9, Folder 86-I)
      Kathy Gillette; Rex Holloway; Linda Oakley
    - What's Different about the Lesbian Culture? (Box 9, Folder 86-J)
      Janna MacAuslan, coordinator
    - Homophobia in the High School: Kids/Counselors (Box 9, Folder 86-K)
      Ray Johnson
    - Human Sexuality: Values, Diversities, and Ironies (Box 9, Folder 86-L)
      Martin Weinberg, PhD
    - How to Mount a Campaign Promoting Legislation to Protect Gays and Lesbians (Box 9, Folder 86-M)
      Keeston Lowery
    - Grant Writing for Your Group (Box 9, Folder 86-N)
      Tom Sauerman, PhD
    - Opening Session and Closing Luncheon (Box 9, Folder 86-O)
    - Plenary Session on Politics (2 tapes) (Box 9, Folder 86-P)
      Barbara Roberts, Secretary of State; Keeston Lowery, Right to Privacy PAC; Nancy Ryles, State Senator; Dick Springer, State Representative; Gary MacDonald, AIDS Action Council
    - Plenary Session on AIDS (2 tapes) (Box 9, Folder 86-Q)
      Gary MacDonald; Estill Deitz, MD; Tom Koberstain, Cascade AIDS Project
    - Worship Service and Plenary Session on Religion (2 tapes) (Box 9, Folder 86-R)
      Dr. George Edwards, moderator; Dr. Jon Anderson, Presbyterian; Marcia Moskowitz, Jewish; Bishop Melvin Wheatley, Methodist; Father Chris Johnson, Roman Catholic; Dr. Eldon Olson, Lutheran
    - Development of Sexual Orientation (Box 9, Folder 86-S)
      Dr. Martin Weinberg of the Kinsey Institute
  - 1987 P-FLAG National Convention, Washington, DC, 23-26 October
    - Lobbying: How to Get Your Views Across (Box 9, Folder 87-1)
      Eric Rosenthal; Kim Elliot; Bob Bingaman
    - Effective Leadership Styles for Chapter Board Members (Box 9, Folder 87-2)
      Tom Sauerman, EdD
    - Gay and Lesbian Coupling (Box 9, Folder 87-3)
      Betty Caldwell, MA; Norma Kearby, MD; Thomas Stanley, JD; Rev. Sydney Wilde-Nugent
    - Educating Children and Teenagers about AIDS (Box 9, Folder 87-4)
      Andy Humm; Dorothy Ward-Wimmer, RN
    - Reaching Out to Minority Families of Gays/Lesbians (Box 9, Folder 87-5)
      Rev. Renee McCoy; Raquel Sosa Palmer, ACSW
    - Creative Fundraising and Other Money Issues (Box 9, Folder 87-6)
      Barry Forbes; Kimberly Webster
    - The Other Side of the Closet: Being Married to a Gay (Box 9, Folder 87-7)
      Janet Fulmer, LCSW; Rev. Jane Vennard
    - Gay and Lesbian Civil Rights (Box 9, Folder 87-8)
      Eric Rosenthal; Eric Hamberg; Jane Dolkart, JD
    - Coping Mechanisms of Gay/Lesbian Clients (Box 9, Folder 87-9)
      Jeffry Akman, MD
    - Confronting Homophobia in the Church: Building a Movement for Change (Box 9, Folder 87-10)
      Rev. Mark Bowman, M. Div.
    - Effective Public Relations (Box 9, Folder 87-11)
      Jay Clark, JD; Philip Dufour; Leon Goodman; James Kapplin; Ola Seifert
    - Loving and Caring for a Person with AIDS (Box 9, Folder 87-12)
      Bill Ceyrolles, ACSW; Ray Chavez; Betty Holloran; Kathy Neale
    - Repealing Sodomy Laws in Your State Through Coalition Building (Box 9, Folder 87-13)
      Stuart Harvey; Peri Jude
    - Gay/Lesbian Youth and Adults in Social Science Systems (Box 9, Folder 87-14)
      Stefan Wade, MSW, LCSW
    - Organizing a Workshop for Young Adults: Coming Out to Your Parents (Box 9, Folder 87-15)
      Susan Sauerman; Tom Sauerman, EdD; Marjorie Tompkins
    - The Federal Response to AIDS (Box 9, Folder 87-16)
      Maggie Donohue, RN; Jeffrey Levi; Steve Smith, JD; James Gottlieb; William Bailey
    - Suicide and Isolation: Mental Health Issues of Gay/Lesbian Youth (Box 9, Folder 87-17)
      Wayne Pawlowski, ACSW
    - Chemical Dependency: Lesbians, Gay Men, and the Family (Box 9, Folder 87-18)
      Barbara O'Neil; Nancy O'Neil, LPN; Joan Smith, RN
    - Friends of Gays: Their Unique Role in the Community (Box 9, Folder 87-19)
      Elizabeth Buie, MS; Mary Dougherty, MSW; Rev. Reah Dougherty
    - Lesbian and Gay Parenting (Box 9, Folder 87-20)
      Rachel Melechen, MA; Lori Rolnick, MA; Wayne Schwandt, M.Div.; Susan Silber, JD; Paul Smith, MSW
    - Lobbying: How to Get Your Views Across (Box 9, Folder 87-21)
      Carlton Lee; Doug Cahn; Pat Reuss
    - Helping Gay/Lesbian High School Students (Box 9, Folder 87-22)
      Stefan Wade, MSW, LCSW; Molly Webster
    - The Politics of Homosexuality (Box 9, Folder 87-23)
      Vic Basile; Jonathan Katz; Rev. Renee McCoy; Amy and Dick Ashworth
    - Annual Meeting Luncheon (Box 9, Folder 87-24)
      Effi Barry, wife of DC Mayor, Marion Barry
    - Note: tape 87-25 does not exist
    - Awards Luncheon (Box 9, Folder 87-26)
      Congressman Ted Weiss (D-NY)
    - Biological Factors in Psychosexual Development (Box 9, Folder 87-27)
      June Reinisch, PhD, Director of the Kinsey Institute
    - Banquet Speakers (Box 9, Folder 87-28)
      Leo Goodman, Master of Ceremonies; Mayor Marion Barry of DC; Dr. Michael Samuels for Surgeon General C. Everett Koop; Dr. Franklin Kameny
    - Banquet Entertainment (Box 9, Folder 87-29)
      Romanovsky and Phillips; Gay Men's Chorus of Washington, DC
  - 1988 P-FLAG National Convention, Chicago, IL, 7-10 October
    - Pathway to Healing: Dealing with Grief (Box 9, Folder 88-A)
      Rev. Carl Melrose, SJ and Rev. Ann Showalter of AIDS National Interfaith Network
    - An Unlikely Partnership: Evangelical Religion and Homosexuality (Box 9, Folder 88-B)
      Gregory Doxy, Lorrie, and Mary
    - Chemical Dependency in the Gay Community (Box 9, Folder 88-C)
      Joan Henderson
    - Strategies for Educational Outreach to Minorities (Box 10, Folder 88-D)
      Leon White
    - Parents Coming Out: The Effect on Society (Box 10, Folder 88-E)
      Carolyn Griffin, Arthur and Marian Wirth, authors of Beyond Acceptance
    - How to Plan Regional/Mini Conferences (Box 10, Folder 88-F)
    - Legal Rights for Nontraditional Couples (Box 10, Folder 88-G)
      Jill Metz, attorney
    - Building Relationships: Coping with Crisis in the Gay Community (Box 10, Folder 88-H)
      William Ledford, PhD; Rita Rogan, PhD
    - Organizing for Political Empowerment (Box 10, Folder 88-I)
      Ron Sable, MD; Jesus Garcia, Alderman; Peggy Baker; Carole Powell
    - Educating Teachers about Gay and Lesbian Youth (Box 10, Folder 88-J)
      Sue Hunter, PhD
    - Parents' Values, Children's Values: Is Gayness a Gift of God? (Box 10, Folder 88-K)
      Rev. Timm Peterson, M.Div.
    - Note: tape 88-L does not exist
    - The Lesbian: An Historical Overview (Box 10, Folder 88-M)
      Marie Kuda
    - Rebel with a Cause: S/SGT Perry Watkins vs. The U.S. Army (Box 10, Folder 88-N)
      S/SGT Perry Watkins; Joe Schuman, attorney
    - Perspectives on the Gay/Lesbian Community (Box 10, Folder 88-O)
      Sarah Craig and Chris Cothran of the "Windy City Times"
    - How Internalized Homophobia Affects Gays/Lesbians (Box 10, Folder 88-P)
      Carol Kyrias
    - A Mother Shares Her Story: Personal Reflections on Coping with AIDS (Box 10, Folder 88-Q)
      Mary Fleming
    - On Being In laws: Gay Couples and their Families (Box 10, Folder 88-R)
      Bruce Koff and Mitchell Channon
    - AIDS Update (Box 10, Folder 88-S)
      Marcia Lipetz, moderator; Ron Sable, MD; Jim Karpiak, AIDS Foundation of Chicago
    - Luncheon/Annual Meeting (Box 10, Folder 88-T)
      William Winter, Denver P-FLAG, speaker
    - Interfaith Worship Service (Box 10, Folder 88-U)
      Jim Bussen; Anita Hill; Fr. Michael Jacobson; Peter Kessler; Norman Sandfield; Dr. Emilie Townes
    - Building a Movement for Change within the Major Religious Denominations (Box 10, Folder 88-V)
      Bishop Melvin Wheatley (United Methodist Church retired), moderator; Dr. Faye Asquith; Marrett Brick, World Congress of Gay/Lesbian Jewish Organizations; Fr. Ken Heavey, Order of Friars Minor
    - Report on the Gay and Lesbian Youth Project (Box 10, Folder 88-W)
      Gilbert Herdt, PhD; Andrew Boxer, Michael Reese Hospital and Medical Center
    - Banquet and Awards Ceremony (Box 10, Folder 88-X)
      Darrel Yates Rist, keynote speaker; Elinor Lewallen, P-FLAG president, "Swan Song"
    - Banquet Entertainment (Box 10, Folder 88-Y)
      Windy City Gay Men's Chorus; Elinor Lewallen, P-FLAG President, "Swan Song"
  - 1989 P-FLAG National Convention, Detroit, MI, 20-23 October
    - AIDS and Legal Issues (Box 10, Folder 89-1)
      Robert Tighe, JD
    - Religion, A Concern of Parents (Box 10, Folder 89-2)
      Sr. Marilyn Bergt, CDP
    - Gay Brothers and Lesbian Sisters (Box 10, Folder 89-3)
      M. Gay Bossart, MA; Deborah Harris
    - Blessings of Homophile Couples (Box 10, Folder 89-4)
      Rev. Walter Lee-Szymanski
    - Living Well Every Day (Box 10, Folder 89-5)
      Scott McCready
    - Long Term Relationships (Box 10, Folder 89-6)
      Dr. Norma Kearby; Betty Caldwell; Karen Baker, MSW; Cecy Ewing, BS
    - A Father and His Son (Box 10, Folder 89-7)
      Isadore and Kevyn Aucoin
    - A Mother and Her Daughter (Box 10, Folder 89-8)
      Eleanor, MA, LittD, and Melanie, MDiv., ThD, Morrison
    - Reaching Out to the Black Community (Box 10, Folder 89-9)
      Barbara Hollie, MSN, RN; Rev. Renee McCoy
    - Making Discussion Groups Work (Box 10, Folder 89-10)
      Katherine McConkey
    - Keeping Peace within Your Organization (Box 10, Folder 89-11)
      Donald Bossart, PhD
    - Healing Power of Humor (Box 10, Folder 89-12)
    - Chemical Dependency and Homosexuality (Box 10, Folder 89-13)
      Joseph F. Lempicki, MA, LLP
    - Spouses and Their Journeys (Box 10, Folder 89-14)
      Rev. Jane Vennard, MDiv; Pat Tupper, MLS; Beth Gaiser, MEd
    - Celebration: Homosexuality Is a Gift (Box 10, Folder 89-15)
      Tim Wilson; Marge Work
    - Two Sons and Their In-Laws (Box 10, Folder 89-16)
      Mr. and Mrs. M. and Brad Boekeloo; Dr. and Mrs. A. and Stanley Drake
    - The Dance of Homophobia (Box 10, Folder 89-17)
    - A Gay Father and His Children (Box 10, Folder 89-18)
      Thomas Trocchio, PhD with Lara and Bret Trocchio
    - Racism in the Gay Community (Box 10, Folder 89-19)
      Marc Loveless
    - Endings and How to Survive (Box 10, Folder 89-20)
      Benna Kisin
    - Going Home for the Holidays (Box 10, Folder 89-21)
      Dale Ross, MSW
    - Working for Social Change in Our Communities (Box 10, Folder 89-22)
      David Feltman; Jean Durgin-Clinchard; Eric Rosenthal; Jim Cernohlavek
    - Future Directions for Sexuality: Beyond the Biology (Box 10, Folder 89-23)
      Sylvia S. Hacker, PhD
    - Convention Luncheons (Box 10, Folder 89-24)
      Dick Ashworth, Paulette Goodman, plus many touching and inspirational comments by attendees
    - Banquet and Speaker: "Lift up Your Hearts" (Box 10, Folder 89-25)
      Rev. Dr. Anne Garrison
    - Banquet Entertainment; Ecumenical Worship Service (Box 10, Folder 89-26)
      Detroit Together Gay Men's Chorus; Dr. James Cox, Kelly and Company Choir
    - Public Knowledge, Attitudes, and Behaviors Related to AIDS and HIV (Box 10, Folder 89-27)
      Susan M. Blake, PhD
    - How to Respond to Families Living with AIDS/ARC/HIV Positivity (2 tapes) (Box 10, Folder 89-28)
      Sara D. Winter, MD, facilitator; Don and Gay Bossart; Marcia Middell; Pat Padock; Carol Tipton
  - 1990 P-FLAG National Convention, Anaheim, CA, 12-14 October
    - Plenary Session: Youth (Box 10, Folder 90-1)
      Joyce Hunter, MSW; Virginia Uribe, PhD
    - Self-Empowerment: Development of Peer Support for Gay/Lesbian Youth (Box 10, Folder 90-2)
      Paul Burnett; Holly Hauff; Todd Layland
    - A Positive Approach: Loving and Supporting the HIV+ Family Member (Box 10, Folder 90-3)
      Paul Kent Froman, PhD; Dina Bachelor Evan, MA
    - Creating a Fundraising Strategy (Box 10, Folder 90-4)
      Pat Callahan; David Feltman
    - Violence Against Gays and Lesbians (Box 10, Folder 90-5)
      Captain Mitchell Groveson; Thomas J. Coleman, Jr. JD
    - Outreach to Public Schools (Box 10, Folder 90-6)
      Jean Durgin-Clinchard; Mitzi Henderson; Hank Wilson
    - Coming Out in the Nineties (Box 10, Folder 90-7)
      Rob Eichberg, PhD
    - How Parents Cope with the News: Two Studies of Parents of Gay Children (Box 10, Folder 90-8)
      Michael Albert; Kathy Zimmerman
    - Understanding Cultural Diversity: Homosexuality and the Asian/Pacific Perspective (Box 10, Folder 90-9)
      Terry Gock, PhD
    - Saturday Luncheon and Annual Meeting - missing (Box 10, Folder 90-10)
    - Meeting the Needs of Homeless Gay/Lesbian Youth (Box 10, Folder 90-11)
      Teresa DeCrescenzo, MSW; Gary Kain, MS
    - Family Communication: AIDS and HIV Infection (Box 10, Folder 90-12)
      Norman Gray, Jr, MS; Denise Penn
    - Leadership Skills: How to Avoid Burnout (Box 10, Folder 90-13)
      Paulette Goodman; Tom Sauerman
    - How to Enhance Media Coverage (Box 10, Folder 90-14)
      Carol Anderson, JD
    - Educating Law Enforcement about Gays/Lesbians (Box 10, Folder 90-15)
      Thomas J. Coleman, Jr.; Captain Mitchell Grobeson
    - Chemical Dependency Issues: Gays/Lesbians and the Family (Box 10, Folder 90-16)
      Rev. Thom Harshman
    - Understanding and Supporting Spouses of Gays/Lesbians (Box 10, Folder 90-17)
      Susan Rodgers, MA; Sue Christiansen
    - Native American Cultures: Homosexuality and the Family (Box 10, Folder 90-18)
      Phil Tingley, MSW; Ron Rowell; Tom Lidot; Ann Sisk, MA
    - Banquet and Entertainment (Box 10, Folder 90-19)
    - Non-Sectarian Celebration: Los Angeles Gay Men's Chorus (Box 10, Folder 90-20)
    - Plenary Session: HIV and AIDS (Box 11, Folder 90-21)
    - A Historical Perspective of the Gay/Lesbian Identity (Box 11, Folder 90-22)
      Judith Doyle, MS
    - Social Action: Coming Out about HIV (Box 11, Folder 90-23)
      Sue Caves; Rick Hersey
    - How to Coordinate an Effective Speaker's Bureau (Box 11, Folder 90-24)
      Jim Boone, PhD
    - A History of the Gay/Lesbian Movement (Box 11, Folder 90-25)
      Stuart Timmons; Jim Kepner
    - Breaking Down Stereotypes: Gay/Lesbian Role Models (Box 11, Folder 90-26)
      Jim Fain, MA, MFCC; Betty Caldwell, PhD; Dr. Norma Kearby, MD; Captain Mitchell Grobeson; Tim Curran
    - Self-Esteem and Acceptance (Box 11, Folder 90-27)
    - Lesbian and Gay Parents (Box 11, Folder 90-28)
      Andre Jacinto; Sue Matranga-Watson; Jude Watson; Doug McIntosh
    - Coming Out to the Latino Family (Box 11, Folder 90-29)
      Mike Moreno; Terri de la Pena; Camille Loya
    - Sunday Luncheon - missing (Box 11, Folder 90-30)
    - Creating Change for Gay Youth (Box 11, Folder 90-31)
      Mark Paul Lehman
    - How to Support Families Affected by HIV: Update on the Family Aids Project (Box 11, Folder 90-32)
      Lenore Pomerance
    - Charter Development (Box 11, Folder 90-33)
      Harriet Dart
    - Educating Public Officials and Opinion Leaders (Box 11, Folder 90-34)
      Pat Callahan; Eric Rosenthal
    - Coming Out to the Congregation: Parents of Gays/Lesbians in the Clergy (Box 11, Folder 90-35)
      James Cernohlavek and Joyce Miller (United Church of Christ); Bob and G.A. Hawthorn (Methodist); Oliver Powell (United Church of Christ)
    - Sexuality: Current Trends and Theories (Box 11, Folder 90-36)
      John Flower, PhD; Nancy Adkins, PhD; Mona Coates, PhD
    - Children of Gays/Lesbians (Box 11, Folder 90-37)
      Jim Fain, MA, MFCC; Samantha Brown, and her mother, Gantry; Jon Tomas; Adam Anderson, and his mother, Carol
    - Moral and Religious Issues Surrounding AIDS/HIV in the African-American Community (Box 11, Folder 90-38)
      Bobby Smith; Clara Alee
    - Closing Session (Box 11, Folder 90-39)
    - When HIV-AIDS Touches Your Family (Box 11, Folder 90-A)
      Fall 1990
    - Accepting Your Gay or Lesbian Child (Box 11, Folder 90-A122)
      Parents Share Their Stories
  - 1991 P-FLAG National Convention, Charlotte, NC, 12-14 October
    - Welcome and Plenary: Personal Empowerment (Box 11, Folder 91-1)
      Harvey Gantt; Rev. Dr. Carter Heyward
    - Same Sex Love in Literature and History (Box 11, Folder 91-2)
      Donald Mager, PhD